你要用 Android Studio 来创建详细界面
You're going to use Android Studio to create the
点击新建Activity  选择Blank Activity with Fragement
detail activity from the blank activity with fragment template.
下一步要求设置它的Hierarchical Parent
The template asks for the hierarchical parent of detail
这个设置设定了这个Activity向上返回到哪
activity, which defines the up button noted by the
同时让左上方按钮变成了一个返回键
app icon, and a left pointing carrot here. But
这里的向上什么意思呐  你把
what does up mean? If you mapped out a
这个程序中几个屏幕之间的层级目录画一下
hierarchy of all screens in the sunshine app, the
根位置应该是 MainActivity  它的子视图
root of the tree would be the main activity, and
应该是 DetailActivity
it's child would be the detail activity. So, the
当你在MainActivyty主视图上时候
app goes to the main activity. While the back button
返回按钮的效果是一样的  它会让你返回主屏幕
can achieve the same effect, it can also bring
或者根据你最近的打开的程序跳转到其他的应用上去
you back home or to another app, depending on your
向上在应用里他会让你返回到父级
history of screens. Up will always navigate you within
不论你是从哪里切换到这个屏幕来的
the same app to the parent, regardless of how you
现在就创建这个 DetailActivity 类吧
arrived at this screen. Create the detail activity now,
然后看看它是怎样在 AndroidMainfest.xml 文件中
and look at how the activity is declared in the
定义的
Android manifest file.